export const binary_practice_questions = [
    {
        question: "Question 1: What is the binary number 0101 equal to?",
        correct_answer: "5",
        wrong_answer1: "7",
        wrong_answer2: "3",
        wrong_answer3: "4"
    },
    {
        question: "Question 2: What is the binary number 1111 equal to?",
        correct_answer: "15",
        wrong_answer1: "10",
        wrong_answer2: "12",
        wrong_answer3: "19"
    },
    {
        question: "Question 3: What is the sum of this binary addition? 010 + 001",
        correct_answer: "011",
        wrong_answer1: "100",
        wrong_answer2: "010",
        wrong_answer3: "001"

    },
    {
        question: "Question 4: What is the sum of this binary addition? 1010 + 0010",
        correct_answer: "1100",
        wrong_answer1: "1011",
        wrong_answer2: "1110",
        wrong_answer3: "1010"
    },
    {
        question: "Question 5: What is the sum of this binary subtraction in decimal in two's compliment? 111 + 001",
        correct_answer: "1000",
        wrong_answer1: "000",
        wrong_answer2: "1110",
        wrong_answer3: "1001"
    }
    
]

export const binary_quiz_questions = [
    {
        question: "Question 1: What is this number 9 in binary (unsigned)?",
        correct_answer: "1001",
        wrong_answer1: "1010",
        wrong_answer2: "0101",
        wrong_answer3: "0110"
    },
    {
        question: "Question 2: What is the number 1100 (unsigned) in decimal?",
        correct_answer: "12",
        wrong_answer1: "13",
        wrong_answer2: "14",
        wrong_answer3: "11"
    },
    {
        question: "Question 3: What is the number 1100 (twos compliment) in decimal?",
        correct_answer: "-4",
        wrong_answer1: "-5",
        wrong_answer2: "4",
        wrong_answer3: "-3"
    },
    {
        question: "Question 4: What is the sum of 1100 + 0011 (unsigned) in decimal?",
        correct_answer: "15",
        wrong_answer1: "17",
        wrong_answer2: "12",
        wrong_answer3: "13"
    },
    {
        question: "Question 5: What is the sum of 1100 + 0011 (twos compliment) in decimal?",
        correct_answer: "-1",
        wrong_answer1: "-2",
        wrong_answer2: "2",
        wrong_answer3: "3"
    }
    
]